[{"answer": "my friend, Gaff", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You know where I been.  I been on vacation", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Police", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Police man", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "When might that be", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh!  Day after tomorrow", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Do you have something against science", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "And what in your estimation works", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "But in your profession that is a risk", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Like you said, Mr. my friend, a machine can be a hazard.  The Voigh", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "The machine works.  She is", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Listen, I could make you a long list of complaints about this fucken city but I still rather be here than up there", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "They'll change the limit before I change my mind", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I know you think it complicates your work, but I'm here to help", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I think you need more help than you've got", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Book the good ones for where", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What shows", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "How about breakfast, I was just going to make some", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh, no bother, I'd be glad to", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Sorry", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I'm doing okay", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I told you I'd come back", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You didn't hear me.  You were sleeping", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Show me something", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Like..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Have you ever cleaned your apartment", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It appears to be dirty", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Andies only simulate suffering", "docId": "Blade-Runner.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No, I don't", "qsentId": 30}]